ghbase.com 2019-04-19

# Privacy Policy » GhBase•com™

Privacy Policy for ghbase.com

At ghbase.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by ghbase.com and how it is used.

 **What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter, and we will only use your email to send you articles from our website only.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**  
ghbase.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on ghbase.com.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to ghbase.com and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on ghbase.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

ghbase.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. ghbase.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

 **Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Email: ghbasetv@gmail  
Phone: 233 54 619 3019
